Inca-chan, it's been a while.
インカちゃん、久々
It's been a while.
久しぶりです
What, do you have a cold?
何、風邪ひいてるの?
No, I'm fine.
いえ、元気です
I'm fine?
元気です?
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
How are you doing?
元気してる?
Why are you wearing a mask today?
何で今日マスクしてるの?
Because it's a little embarrassing.
ちょっと恥ずかしいから
Because it's embarrassing?
恥ずかしいから?
Seriously?
マジで?
Take off your mask.
マスク取ってみて
got it.
わかりました
It's still cute.
相変わらず可愛いね
Inca-chan is still cute.
インカちゃん、相変わらず可愛いね
Today, are you nervous today?
今日はさ、 今日はさ、 緊張してるの?
I'm nervous.
緊張してます
Are you nervous?
緊張してるの?
I see.
そっか
Today's cute though.
今日の可愛いだけど
I'm wondering what I should do today,
今日はさ、 何しようかなって思ってるんだけど、
The other day, we just had some sex, right?
この間はさ、普通にさ、 ちょっとセックスしたじゃん?
yes.
はい
So, the economic number is 2 people, right?
で、景気人数2人でしょ?
There were three of us.
3人だったんだったじゃん
All at once?
一気に?
I want to do it all at once.
一気にしたいな
I was thinking that I wanted to break through a little bit with one hand.
片手ちょっと突破したいなって思っててね、
As for the old man.
おっさんはね
I'm thinking about it, man.
ちょっと 思ってるんだね、おっさん
So, I'm thinking, ``What about multiple people?''
で、おっさん思ってて、 複数人どうでしょうって思ってるんです
But what do you think?
けど、 どう?
I want to try it.
やってみたい
Do you really think so?
本当に思ってる?
yes.
はい
It's a little hard to answer because there are so many people.
ちょっといっぱい人いるから、 ちょっと答えづらい?
I want to try it.
やってみたい
Want to try it?
やってみたい?
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
By the way, even if there are multiple people, it's not just three people.
ちなみに複数人つっても、 3人とかじゃなくてさ、
I thought I'd like to try making a copy.
ちょっとコーピーをしてみたいなって思って
What do you think?
どうですか?
I want to try it.
やってみたい
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Are you a little nervous?
ちょっと緊張する?
It's really uncomfortable outside.
やっぱ外気まずいね
It's really awkward.
めっちゃ気まずい
Let's go to the hotel now.
もうホテル入ろうかじゃ
But, there are still only those five people.
だけどさ、 まだその5人っていうのさ、
I'm not ready.
用意できてないんよ
I guess I should procure it locally.
っていうのもさ、 現地調達しようかな、
That's what I'm thinking, but I can talk to you.
って思ってるんだけどさ、 話しかけられる
From me.
私からね
Uncle also helps.
おじさんも手伝う
Will you try your best?
頑張ってみる?
Awkward?
気まずい?
Okay, then just put it in.
分かった、じゃあ入れだけでいい
The old man will call out to you, so let's do our best.
おじさん声かけるからさ、 ちょっと頑張ってやってみよう
Otherwise, the five of us won't be able to gather together.
じゃないとだって5人集まんないから
Today, the other day, there was someone who acted as an actor.
今日 ね、この間さ、男優さんやってくれた人いるしさ、
acquaintance?
知り合い?
I know you.
知り合いです
acquaintance?
知り合い?
There's one person, but I can do it with up to three people.
なんか人が1人いて、 3人まではできるんだけどさ、
I thought I would like two more people.
あと2人ちょっと欲しいなと思って
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
yes.
はい
I guess I'll just give it a try anyway.
とりあえずやってみるだけやってみようか
My hair is fine.
髪大丈夫です
Are you okay.
大丈夫
Inka-chan's hair is messy so she can't be caught.
インカちゃんが髪乱れてるから、 引っ掛けられないとか、
That's not the problem.
そういう問題じゃないから
I'm a little tired.
ちょっと疲れたね
I'm tired of walking.
歩き疲れたね
That's outrageous.
とんでもないです
I'm trying my best to talk to you, but
頑張って声かけてみてはいるけどさ、
It's a bit of a shame.
なかなかちょっとかまんないね
I don't mind.
かまんない
Shall we try a little harder?
もうちょっと頑張ってみる?
Hold on a little longer.
もうちょっとかまって
Okay, then let's go.
よし、じゃあ行こう
Let's keep looking for it.
どんどん探しに行こう
What is that?
あれは?
It's over there, it's over there.
あそこにさ、 あそこにいるじゃん
A person with a black top and bottom.
黒い上下の人
Yes, that's fine, isn't it?
そうだし、いいんじゃないですか
I feel like my uncle isn't doing well,
おじさんがちょっといけないような気もするから、
I went there with the actor.
男優さんと2人に行ってきて
Just change the camera.
ちょっとカメラ交換
Rika-chan,
りかちゃんさ、
Hey, let's muster up our courage and try our best to say something.
ね、 勇気を振り払って、 ちょっと 頑張って声かけよう
If you don't catch it, it won't start.
捕まえないことにはさ、 始まんないから
I can't go home because I can't start.
始められないとして帰れないから
Just try your best.
ちょっと頑張って
I'll go with you too.
俺も一緒に行くからさ
Let's go for a while, then.
ちょっと行こうか、じゃあ
Let's go together.
一緒に行きましょう
Let's go then.
じゃあ行こう
Come on.
おいで
sorry.
すみません
Is the time okay now?
今、時間大丈夫ですか?
Yes, it's okay though.
はい、大丈夫ですけど
What were you doing to Tsunami just now?
今、つなみに何されてたんですか?
I was drinking with a friend, and I finished my drink.
友人と飲んでて、 飲み終わったんですけど、
I didn't have enough to drink, so I was looking for a place to eat.
飲み足りなくて、ちょっと店探してたんですけど
I was looking for the next restaurant to drink again.
飲み直しっていうか、 次のお店を探してた
It's early, isn't it?
時間早いですもんね
I still had some time.
まだちょっと時間あったので
It's sudden, but
突然ですけど、
It's not that big, but
あ んまり大きくいっちゃいないんですけど、
I'll have sex with this girl
この女の子と セックスしてくれる、
I've been looking for a guy to have sex with,
セックスしてくれる 男子をちょっと探してまして、
It's a bit of a cool play, but
ちょっとスクスープレイなんですけど、
We didn't have enough people, so I thought there might be someone better.
ちょっと人数足んなくて、 ちょっと良い方いないかなと思って、
Are you starting now?
今からですか?
Starting now.
今からです
It seemed like he was a little bored, so I thought it was a good thing.
ちょっと暇そうにされてたので、 良 かったと思って、
What do you think?
どうですかね?
It's okay though.
大丈夫ですけど
OK?
大丈夫 ですか?
yes.
はい
Please tell us a few words about the silver store.
銀貨店の一言お願いします
One word.
一 言
Please if it's okay with me.
私が良ければお願いします
thank you.
よろしく お願いします
Well then, the negotiation has been concluded.
じゃあ、 交渉成立ということで
Also, I need to grab a few more people.
あとね、 もう何人かちょっと 掴まなきゃいけないんで、
Please let me know your contact information,
ちょっと連絡先 教えてもらって、
So, I'll contact you again when the number of people decreases a bit.
それで ちょっと 人数下がったらまたちょっと 連絡します
So, can I kill your time here?
んで、 時間この辺で潰してもらっていいですか?
Understood.
分かりました
Is the time okay?
時間 大丈夫ですか?
Please wait a moment.
ちょっと待っててください
thank you.
ありがとうございます
Good for you, Mr. Silver Store.
良かったね、銀貨店さん
It was good.
良かったです
I got it anyway.
とりあえずゲットしたね
Let's try a little harder.
もうちょっと頑張ろう
Ginkin-chan, you've already managed to grab your first one.
銀貨ちゃん、 もう一人目掴めちゃったじゃん
That's amazing.
すごいじゃん
You did it.
やったね
This is how it is, this is how it is.
この調子だよ、この調子
Let's do our best for one more person.
あと一人頑張ろう
Let's do our best one more time.
あと 一人頑張ろう
You're used to it.
慣れたね
I've gotten used to it.
慣れちゃいましたね
I want to go to a hotel these days,
この頃もうホテルも行きたいからさ、
I called out to about 3 or 4 other groups, 3 or 4 people, 4 or 5 people, and
あと3、4組、 3、4人、4、5人 くらいちょっと声掛けて、
If so, let's go somewhere else.
そうだったら、 違うところ行こうよ
I'll use it somewhere else.
もう違うところ使う
Let's do our best today with 4P.
4Pで今日頑張ろう
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
I guess it's better if you don't have an uncle after all?
やっぱりおじさんいない方が いいのかな?
Is it better to have two people with the person who works with you?
対応さんと二人の方がいいのかな?
What do you think?
どうなんですかね
Shall we go again?
もう一回行ってみようか
Uncle, please pick up someone who looks good.
おじさん、良さそうな人、 ピックアップしてください
I was told to wait and changed my mind, but I'm also an old man.
待って言われて変わったけどさ、 俺もおじさんだけどね
Yeah.
うん
You were a little relieved that one person was caught, right?
一人捕まえられたから、 ちょっとほっとしたでしょ?
I agree.
そうですね
I was relieved.
ほっとしました
I felt like it wasn't working at all and I didn't know what to do.
全然ダメでどうしようって感じだったけどさ、
Somehow.
なんとか
It's a bit sudden, and I think your friend will be surprised.
ちょっと突然過ぎて、 お友人びっくりすると思うけど、
If you have the time, I don't think you can refuse this.
時間さえあれば、 これは断る話ではないと思うんだよね
Well then, let's go for a while.
じゃあちょっと行こうか
Yes, let's go.
はい、行きましょう
There's another person over there who seems to be wasting his time.
あそこにまた、暇をもてやましてそうな人がいるからね
Shall we go for a while?
ちょっと行きましょうか
Let's go.
行ってみましょう
Let's go together.
一緒に行こう
Let's do our best.
頑張ろう
頑張りましょう
I'll call out to you first.
最初俺声かけるから
yes.
はい
Sorry.
すいません
OK?
大丈夫ですか?
Isn't that suspicious?
怪しいもんじゃないですか?
What are you doing now?
今、何してますか?
I'm looking at Matt now and wondering how far I should walk.
今、マットを見て、 どこまで歩こうかなと
walk?
歩く?
How far do you walk?
どこまで歩く?
I was just taking a walk.
散歩してただけなんですけど
Did you come here for a walk?
散歩でここ来たんですか?
that's right.
そうです
I think I'll walk home again.
また歩いて帰ろうかなと
It's healthy.
健康的ですね
Like walking as a hobby?
趣味散歩みたいな?
that's right.
そうです
Do you feel pretty confident in your physical strength?
体力とか結構自信ある感じですか?
Isn't it about normal?
普通ぐらいじゃないですか
Is this some kind of interview?
これは何かのインタビューですか?
I agree.
そうですね
It's a short interview.
ちょっとしたインタビューなんですけど
Have you gotten to the point?
本題入っちゃったかな?
I asked the person in charge, but I just have to go home.
担当直入に聞くんですけど、 もうあと家帰るだけですよね、
After this.
このあと
It feels like you have time.
時間はある感じですよね
Today is my day off.
今日は休みなんで
By the way, this girl who is with me now,
ちなみに、今の僕と一緒にいる この女の子、
This cute girl is looking for a man to have sex with her.
可愛い子、 この子と セックスしてくれる 男性を探している
Yes, it is.
んです よ
To that extent, yes.
そこまで、はい
OK?
大丈夫ですか?
Do you understand the story?
話理解できてます?
Are you able to swallow it?
飲み込めてます?
Say that again, please.
もう一度お願いします
Looking for a man to have sex with the girl I'm with
僕と一緒にいる 女の子と セックスしてくれる 男性を探して
I'm here.
います
That's the story.
っていう 話です
It's not something suspicious...
怪しいことではなくて...
I feel suspicious now, but it's okay.
今怪しい感じですけど、 大丈夫です
rest assured.
安心してください
What do you think?
どうですかね?
What if you like?
よかったらどうですか?
If you can...
できるのであれば...
Rinka-chan was there for a while, look.
ちょっとりんかちゃんいたよ、ほら
Rinka-chan, please.
りんかちゃん、お願いして
If I come, please.
私が来れば、お願いします
OK?
大丈夫ですか?
Rinka-chan, get it.
りんかちゃん、ゲット
Ah, there you are.
あ、いましたね
Good for you.
よかったね
I was also relieved, kind of.
俺もほっとしたよ、なんか
Well then...
じゃあ、ちょっと...
Hey, wait a minute.
ちょっと、 これ、ちょっと待ってね
Multiple trees are a bit male, and
複数のツレーって、ちょっと 男性あと、
I'm probably alone, or I'm looking for more.
もうね、 ちょっと一人か、 ちょっともっと探しているので、
Can I have your contact information please?
ちょっと連絡先を 教えてもらっていいですか?
I'll let you know once it's decided, and I'll leave it to you for a while.
決まったら次連絡するんで、 ちょっとこの辺にするまで、
Can I have you kill time?
時間を遂げつぶしてもらっていいですか?
yes.
はい
I'll contact you right away.
すぐ連絡します
Sorry, thank you.
すいません、ありがとうございます
Rinka-chan, this is terrible.
りんかちゃん、 やばいね、こまえず
We gathered together.
集まったね
集まっちゃいましたね
It's all thanks to Rinka-chan and Rinka-chan for their hard work.
ちゃん とりんかちゃんが 頑張ってくれたおかげだね
By the way, Rinka-chan hooked it.
ちなみに、 りんかちゃんがひっかけた、
The two of them called out to me and hooked me.
声かけてひっかけたっていう 2人は、
Could you please raise your hand for a moment?
ちょっと手を 上げてもらっていいですか?
Mr. A and Mr. B.
Aさん、Bさんということで
Well, let's start with Mr. A in the front.
じゃあ、まず手前のAさん
Thank you, Mr. A.
Aさん、ありがとうございます
Are you okay, really?
大丈夫ですか、本当に?
It's okay, thank you.
大丈夫です、よろしくお願いします
Do you have experience with multiple people?
複数人とか、経験ありますか?
OK?
大丈夫ですか?
No problem.
問題ないです
Well, Mr. B.
じゃあ、Bさん
OK?
大丈夫ですか?
Same question though.
同じ質問ですけど
it's okay.
大丈夫です
If it wasn't okay, I wouldn't have come.
大丈夫だなかったら、来てないですからね
Do you know Mr. C?
Cさんが、 知り合いますか?
I see.
なるほど
thank you.
ありがとうございます
No, it helped me, on the contrary.
いや、助かりました、逆に
Yes, of course.
はい、当然です
After all, rather than sounding like 4P,
やっぱり、4Pっていう響きより、
5P sounds better, after all.
5Pっていう響きの方が、 やっぱりね、
Because there is.
あるからね
It's impressive.
迫力ありますね
It's impressive, isn't it?
迫力あるでしょ
Take a look around and look behind you.
ちょっと周り見て、後ろの
That's amazing, isn't it?
すごいでしょ
By the way, Rinka-chan looks like this.
ちなみに、 りんかちゃん、こんな感じ
The video is amazing, isn't it?
映像すごいでしょ
That's amazing.
すごいね
For now, it looks like this.
とりあえず、こんな感じです
It's your first time, right?
初めてでしょ
It's your first time.
初めてだよね
Outside, I couldn't really tell, but
外じゃさ、 ちょっと伝わらなかったけど、
As expected, I'm really excited.
やっぱ、 イキイキしてますね
fun?
楽しみ?
I'm looking forward to it.
楽しみです
That was really good.
すごい良かったわ、それは
That was good.
良かったね
Well then, let's have some fun with 5P.
じゃあ、ちょっと5P楽しんじゃおうか
It was my first experience.
初めての経験でね
By the way, I wonder how...
ちなみに、どういう風に、 なんかさ、
I said last time that I like AV.
AVとかさ、 好きって前回言ったじゃん
I like it.
好きです
I've seen these kind of promiscuous people, things like multi-player games.
こういう乱行者っていうかさ、 複数人プレイとかっていうのを見
Do you want to do it?
る の?
I see it sometimes.
たまに見ますね
For example, if you want to play something like this,
例えばだけどさ、 こういうプレイしたいだったりさ、
I kind of admire something like this,
こういうのちょっと 憧れますとかだったりさ、
Is there such a thing?
そういうのってあるの?
But when I see how everyone places them,
でも、みんなに 置かされてるのとか見ると、
I'm really excited.
すごい興奮してる
I see.
なるほどね
That's why.
っていうことなんで
So, everyone, let's do it today.
じゃあ、みなさん今日は、 やってやりましょう
Well then, let's do it.
じゃあ、やっちゃおうか
good?
いい?
yes.
はい
Well then, Riba-chan.
じゃあ、りばちゃん
Will I get killed?
やられちゃう?
I'll get hit.
やられちゃう
You've shot a lot, haven't you?
いっぱい撃ててあるでしょ
Wow, you're touching me so much.
すごい、いっぱい こんなに触られちゃってるね
Are you starting to feel like you're shooting?
撃ってきた気分になってきた?
It's easy now.
もう簡単だね
Everyone, please do whatever you like.
みなさん、もう好きにやっていただいて
It's a little stained, but I'll fix it soon.
ちょっとシミになってますけど、すぐに
yeah?
ん?
what happened?
どうしたの?
Isn't it early?
早くない?
It's already a stain.
もうシミになってる
what happened?
どうしたの?
Were you looking forward to it that much?
そんなに 楽しみにしてたの?
Were you looking forward to it?
楽しみにしたの?
copper?
どう?
There are stains.
シミできちゃってる
It's done.
できちゃってる
So let's all do some dick.
だから、みんなチンコやりましょうよ
There's four of us, dick.
4人だよ、チンコ
Do you want to go pussy?
まんこいく?
show me.
見せて
Are you feeling better now?
もう気持ちよくなってきたの?
It's this way.
こっちだね
I could eat dick.
チンコ食えた
If you want to eat dick, eat dick.
チンコ食えたかったら、チンコ食えて
good?
いい?
Please let me have some extra food.
おまけ食べさせてください
I'm busy.
忙しいよ
Because my dick came.
チンコ来たから
delicious.
おいしい
My dick is the best today.
チ ンコ、今日一番だからね
Hey, hair, hey.
ちょっと、髪の毛さ、ちょっと
More, more.
もっと、もっと
Just the hair is fine.
髪だけいいよ
Eat it.
食べちゃって
Kushitto.
くしっと
Hasanano.
はさなの
Shut up.
く しっと
what happened?
どうしたの?
If this is all you have here, you'll fall right away.
こっちに、これだけだとすぐ落ちちゃうね
That's right, thank you very much.
そうそう、ありがとうございます
It's better to stop.
止まったほうがいい
Sorry, sorry.
ごめん、ごめん
The inside came out too.
中も出てきちゃった
Make the futon ring.
布団のふとん鳴らして
That's no good.
ダメじゃん
No good, right?
ダメでしょ?
If the futon gets wet, everyone will catch a cold.
布団を濡らしたら、みんな風邪引いちゃうじゃん
I'm telling you no.
ダメって言ってんのに
Why did you get it wet?
なんで、濡らしたの?
I'll put it on.
かけるじゃん
Let's all connect with this feeling.
みんな、この気持ちをつなげて
Surround yourself with your dick on the bed.
ベッドの上で、チンコで囲んであげてください
There's a lot of dick, so come on.
チンコれっぱいから、ほら
Make sure to hold hands and mouth properly.
ちゃんと手と口取りを合わすんだよ
Jingrin, come on, let me lick the other one.
ジングリン、ほら、他ののを舐めてあげて
The one that isn't dry, it's about time.
乾いてないやつ、そろそろ
It's four years ago.
この4つ前になっとるわ
Lick it towards your mouth.
舐めなって、口に向けて
So, in front of me, I grabbed a chair and asked her to come in.
で、前、椅子を抱き取り、入ってもらって
The person in front of me licked it for a day.
1日舐めてあげて、前の人が
Yes, let's not transform.
そう、変容しないでおこう
It smells, it's bad, it's licking.
臭いなり、悪いなり、舐めなり
Please do it invisible.
見 えなくやっちゃってください
Pin
ピ ン
Ka-chan, is it about time for your dick to age?
カ ちゃん、そろそろチンコの年齢?
Yeah.
うん
I'll have you go then.
行ってもらう、じゃあ
Pinka-chan.
ピ ンカちゃん
Which dick's age?
どのチンコの年齢?
Hey, just go.
ちょっと、行ってよ
Please put it in order.
順番つけてって
Just put the order in order.
順番だけ、順番つけてよ
Yeah.
うん
Could you please turn towards me for a moment?
ちょっとこっち向いてもらっていい?
Sorry.
ごめんね
Which one should you choose?
どれにする?
Yeah.
うん
Is that better?
そっちがいいの?
Because it's the one that stands the most.
一番立ってるからね
By the way, have a drink.
ちなみに、ちょっと飲むで
So, can I ask you a favor?
じゃあ、お願いしちゃっていいですか?
fun?
楽しみ?
good
いい
Yo.
よ
Bishabisha.
ビ シャビシャ
Have you become shabby?
ビシャビシャになっちゃった?
Then I'll drink it myself.
それから自分が飲みにしよう
That's not enough, isn't it?
足りないでしょ、そのビシャビシャ
It's okay to include that.
それ入れてもいいな
Anything is fine.
何でもいいよ
Well then, you can add some silence.
じゃあ、静寂入れてもいいな
Your mouth is thin.
お口が薄だよ
Is it okay?
いいの?
I cum inside you.
中出しちゃって
That was no good.
ダメだったじゃん
It's no good, but is it okay?
ダメだけどいいの?
Because it feels good.
気持ちいいから
Is it okay to cum inside me because it feels so good?
気持ちいいから中出していいの?
Please let me cum inside you.
どうぞ、中で出してもらって
Is it okay?
いいんですか?
It seems like it's okay.
大丈夫みたいなんで
Don't tell me it's a little close to your stomach.
ちょっとお腹近いって言わないで
It came out.
出てきちゃった
Next time, you can put one in, right?
次、1個入れてもいいでしょう?
Please put it in.
入れてください
Which one can I put in?
どっち入れてもいいの?
What's next?
次 は?
What's the second one?
2番目は?
Which dick?
どっちのチンコ?
This way.
こっち
Well then, please.
じゃあ、お願いしな
please.
お願い
Chin
チン
Ko I'm coming in, Linga-chan.
コ 入ってくるよ、リンガちゃん
Nice, I got a lot of dick today.
いいね、今日チンコいっぱいあって
Thailand is also good.
タイとかも別にいいんですよ
I don't care what you want me to do.
何やってもらってもいいんで
He's pretty good at backing, and he's very picky.
バックとか、結構 食い打ち、気上いとか 得意じゃんね、
Linga-chan.
リンガちゃん
It's out.
出ちゃいましたね
It was amazing the other day.
すご かったもんね、この前
Just do it, here.
やって あげな、ほら
Touch your other hand.
反対の手を触ってあげて
Touch me here.
こっちに触ってあげて
Please step back a little bit here.
こっちに、ちょっと下がってあげて
Because my arms are narrow.
腕狭いから
Seino, Seino.
せーの、せーの
Please come down here.
こっちに下がってあげて
Seino.
せーの
In this state, I want it to rise to the right.
この状態で、右上がりしてほしいの
Please, here.
お願いしな、ほら
Yes, let's come.
はい、来そう
I think the dick under there might fit in.
そこの下のチンコ、入りそうかな
Look around, I want you to put it in me, dick.
ぐるっと見て、入れてほしいな、チンコ
Just like that.
そのまま
This is perfect.
これで、まったかってほら
It's amazing, it's a mess.
すごいね、めちゃくちゃだ
Look, it's dark.
あむげになってほら
Everyone is fine.
みんな元気だね
That's amazing.
すごいね
This turned completely white.
これ 真っ白になっちゃったよ
I'm feeling better again.
また元気になっちゃったね
You're fine.
元 気だね
Sure, again.
すれーとな、また
Then, please.
そしたら、お願いしな
This one please.
こっちをお願いします
please.
お願いします
Is it off now?
今、ずれてるの?
Sorry now.
今、すんな
Please back up.
バ ックでお願いしまーす
Wait, can you lose one leg?
ちょっと、片足やられるの?
a little bit.
ちょっと
Wait, can you do it?
ちょっと、やれるの?
Yes, that's fine.
そう、それでいいよ
difficult.
難しい
If you're interested, fine.
気になったら、いいよ
Did it come out?
出たの?
Chew it with your mouth.
お口でかみしてほら
What should I do?
どうすんの?
That's the one that's melting.
それトロトロしてるやつ
Don't you drink?
飲まない?
Don't you want to cock?
コックンしないの?
He's a good boy.
いい子だね
Come here for a moment.
ちょっとこっち来て
Get up.
起き上がって
how was it?
どうだった?
Did you have feelings?
気持ちがあった?
how was it?
どうだった?
Well, it's not over yet.
っていうかさ、 まだ終わんないんだけどね
Try it, see.
やってみて、ほら
Everyone is fine.
みんな元気だよ
tired?
疲れた?
Still not enough, right?
まだ物足りないでしょ?
Do you still want to be disturbed?
まだおかされたい?
Are you tired?
疲れたの?
Just a little bit?
ちょっとだけ?
Timey round, then, let's do it.
タイミーラウンドじゃあ、やろうか